(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-06T23:00:59.702400",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Oh, you...
There is no one I adore more.
You, who must have risked life and limb
to be here with me forevermore.
The last words I wrote
before I was cast into this endless abyss...
...by the immortals seeking to protect this world
and all of its inhabitants.
Wrapped in darkness, alone,
void of all emotion,
I once more feel a presence
signaling my return.
Love's fervent zeal,
a spark of light in this ocean.
Now there is but little left for you to do
before I am free and we can be together.
And those who trapped me within these pages
shall rue locking away this beauty forever.
Only your love can set me free.
Go, recite the verse before you, quickly.
Must before me you bend and take a knee.
[Title: Love Me, Love Me, Love Me]
Ah...
Once in a far away, far away world
was a collar that coiled like a snake.
I want someone please, I need someone please,
oh, I listened close as it howled in ache.
Please don't be angry and please don't abandon me,
don't leave me here on my own.
It wrapped itself tightly, daily and nightly,
only with praise would it loosen its hold.
I placed at the top of my class,
there's no one left for me to surpass.
Don't I look cute in this dress?
I really, really, really must confess,
it's tightening round my neck.
Give me your love, all of your love!
Give me your love, all you can conjure up!
Give me your love, all of your love,
till you go mad with ecstasy!
All of the hurt, all of the ache,
help me escape, take it away, take it away!
Is there no end to this pain?
Ah...
Grow as you may, but the necklace will stay
just as small as the day it was found.
It's so suffocating, the endless placating.
No one is, no one is ever enough!
Won't lose to anyone, always rank number one.
Aren't you a beautiful child?
Hey!
I'm better than her, I'm better than him.
Oh, everyone come running, gawk at perfection!
Meeting you right after school,
and finally confessing to you...
Ain't it too good to be true?
A girl like me, in love with you,
who's miserable, vulgar, and rude!
Give me your love, all of your love.
Give me your love, you can have everything.
If I have you, I can have you.
Shoulder my load, now yours to behold.
Still not enough, you're not enough,
never enough...
Still I won't lose my hold!
Truly, I'm so sorry!
Give me your love, all of your love.
Give me your love, all you can conjure up!
Give me your love, all of your love,
till you go mad with ecstasy!
I know it hurts, only gets worse.
God, how it hurts, soon you'll be craving...
...the pain!
This is my happiness!
Is this my happiness?
Did you enjoy my lovely song?
I hope you did.
It was for you, after all.
But...
why are you not smiling?
Are you not happy to see me?
Well?
Say something. Answer me!
Who... Who are you?
What?
You don't know who I am?
But everyone knows. You are the one that released me, right?
I'm... I'm sorry.
You're sorry? For what? For releasing me?
No, no, no. For upsetting you.
If I said something wrong, I apologize.
Apologize?
You, who should be amongst my most dearest and beloved followers?
Who has freed me from that prison, who has shown me your love above all others?
You then act like you don't even know who I am?
Why would you toy with my emotions?
I'm... I'm sorry, I'm not sure what you mean.
You're not sure what I mean?
Are you mocking me now?
If you truly do not know who I am...
...then why is it that you set me free?
If not for my love, and if not by your love, then for what?!
Tell me the truth, and the whole truth, now.
No more lies, or there will be consequences.
I-I'm not lying! I swear to you,
I have no idea how I released you.
I just came to the temple to collect rare spices and memories from the many books stowed away here.
By the gods, that's the whole truth.
Extract memories from books?
Are you telling me you're a witch?!
How dare you step foot here!
Even knowing the long history between demons and witches, you still dare step foot here?
I know how witches dare to try and bind my kind.
Would you be foolish enough to dare attempt that on me?
Yeah, so okay, yes, I'm a witch,
but I've never... well, mostly never, tried anything like that! I swear.
And this time, I was not led on by my nature at all. No.
This time it was an angel that told me of this place.
An angel came to me in my dreams.
...told me of an enchanted book with memories stored away here. Can you imagine...
...the knowledge and stories...
...hidden in centuries of memories?
With a prize like that, I had to come find the book, no matter the danger.
Little could I have known the true nature of the book, though.
Enough! I've heard enough.
I believe you are who you say you are: a witch.
But I don't fully believe your childish story.
No angel would ever lead a witch to such a dangerous book.
And I can hardly believe it is just the book and not myself you are after.
I-It's true! An angel came to me in my dreams and told me to come here.
I was drawn to that book with all its power and stories...
...and, well, I guess, you inside it.
The powerful aura it gave off drew me right to it.
How was I to know that the allure was thanks to a demon trapped within its pages?
Who would've guessed?
Though, now that I recount my story, it does seem it really was me who released you.
Speaking of coming and going...
...now that you are free, I think it is time I take my leave of this place.
I'm glad I was able to help free you from...
...from whence you came.
I didn't say you could leave.
You may leave when I say you can leave.
And stop your nervous fidgeting. I'm no fool.
You think I didn't see you reaching for your book of magic?
You, a witch, should know better than anyone...
...that no amount of magic is powerful enough to destroy a demon of my power.
However, you can take some small solace in the fact that...
...if I had wanted you dead, you'd already be so.
The only reason you're still alive is because you helped free me.
Alas, I cannot allow a witch...
...who so obviously came with the intention to bind me to her will...
...leave here freely.
Your story did little to convince me your aims were otherwise.
So, I will give you an ultimatum.
You serve me here, in my hollow temple.
Love me. Adore me. Worship me.
Every living day, give me all the love you have.
Or, I can take your soul right now.
Your choice.
Grimoire... I need you!
Lost in the rain with no umbrella
Night snuffs out your eyes
Can't seem to find your way back home, so
...come in and be my guest
Such a lovely smile spread across your face
...but it's simply forgery
If you need to hide from the world outside
...why not try to be my guest?
Waiting all day long but your friends don't come
...and you're left there all alone
Still you can't jump off from the high rooftop
...so come on and be my guest
And why don't you get the way I step and step and step
With carefully spaced, my feet go tap and tap and tap
They fall nicely with the snap and snap and snap
So lovely, you'll be mesmerized by me
My institution's peaceful as can be
...despite the way that it seems
Both of our quotes and our supports will be concise, clear and clean
Since we're only starting out there's some improbabilities
But just listen up tonight you'll have to stay at least
Though they don't like you, and you know it's true
...still you're at their beck and call
Since you're desperately, giving easily...
...come inside and be my guest
You're the last to choose but you're left confused
...seems that someone took your share
If you want to accuse, cuz you don't have proof
...take a chance and be my guest
On the way back home there's a sweet aroma
...that tempts you off your path
I can't help but laugh cuz I know in fact...
You!
Demon! How dare you kill an innocent?
Excuse me?
I've done no such thing.
Innocent?
I would hardly call a witch who lives for power...
...and binds my kind for her own purposes... innocent.
The very idea is laughable.
Leave.
I have no quarrel with you, so go now...
...in peace, before I change my mind.
A small token for your past bravery and trials.
How gracious.
Don't think I can't see straight through your ploys, though.
You will not escape justice.
Not this time.
You have brought this fight on yourself through your actions, demon.
You have brought all of this on yourself.
For what?
For killing a mere witch?
She was not just a witch!
She was my friend...
...and a kind-hearted person.
And you killed her...
...in cold blood!
Oh?
The legendary Phoenix...
...the mighty, fiery Kiara...
...friends with a witch?
It's almost funny.
Did you not realize...
...it was your witch friend who freed me?
Liar!
She would never do such a ghastly thing!
I trust she would stay away...
...from the dark magics and demonic rituals.
To suggest otherwise is just another one of your dark lies.
She didn't deserve to die.
Poor Phoenix.
Still so trusting of those around you...
...and unable to see through their deceptions.
Your kind spirit constantly deceives you.
That witch was never your friend.
We all know they cannot be trusted.
Even after all these years, you still have not changed.
Still believing in lies and still so easily misled.
Still such a fool.
It is you who is the fool, demon!
Your lust for love and attention...
...continues to lead you down the path of death and destruction.
And you don't even see...
...that you're the one destroying your own happiness.
The gods were right to confine you there.
You, who are still shackled by your lust...
...for love...
Your desire for attention...
Your desire to be worshiped!
I am the Demon of Sound!
How dare you speak to me in such a manner?
It is but right that all should worship me on their knees.
Their love for none but myself.
Leave.
I have heard enough of your falsities.
This is your last warning.
Go now, or you'll be left to rot here forever!
I am not afraid of you,
and I will heed no such warning.
Listen, and listen well, demon.
I will not allow you to claim any more victims.
To be banished in a void was not sufficient enough punishment for you.
No.
Now, I will finish what the gods should have.
Come on and get moving, cuz now I'm on a roll, oh
One chance to choose it, so what you wager above below
You either win or not, can't ever be a draw
Uh, uh, yeah, open the curtains up
Mouths are running, lacking money, mocking with a snicker, snicker
Acting funny, asking if I'm winning, with a "huh?"
Make your bets, black or red, chips to spend, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Raise the stakes, clean that slate, risk your life on a single game
Stay with me, all of it will change
You'll stay, not here to play, don't get in my way, I'm tired of talking
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three
Sit down, sit down
One, two, three, one, two, three
1, 2, 3
I've got skills as cold as ice
You've got to throw your hands up if you can't decide
Going to scare you off as I roll the dice, huh
Pussies got to say goodbye, yeah
Aren't enough, you make a bluff
Enough, enough, enough now
Need a life, a sweet-sweet night
Light it up, up, up now
I'm spinning round, got to avoid the voices in my head
No stopping now, I've just got to win this game instead
Get one's way, ooh...
You bet I'm here to stay
And now it's time to learn your place!
Our streak is running, lucky money
Smoking like a cigar, cigar
Acting funny, answer if I'm quitting, well I'm not!
Make your bet, black or red, chips to spend, yeah yeah yeah yeah
Raise the stakes, play that ace, risk your life on a single game
Stay with me, yeah yeah, your luck will change, you'll see, yeah yeah
I came to play, don't get in my way, I've always counted...
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3
Sit down, sit down
Pussies say goodbye-bye
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3
Sit down, sit down
I'm so sorry.
IRyS... It has been so long.
Nerissa!
I'm so, so sorry this happened to you.
It was not my intention.
What do you mean?
What was not your intention?
This... you being imprisoned...
then the witch... Kiara, too...
What? Are you saying you sent
the Phoenix here to slay me?!
No, I didn't! Well, yes, but
it was not my intention.
IRyS, what are you trying to tell me?
That you tried to kill me?
You were supposed to be my friend!
We've been friends since the beginning!
Yes, of course!
You sent Kiara to kill me?!
No, no!
Then what?!
Be clear!
Or is this how you greet your beloved
friend after so long?
No, I... I would never
send someone to kill you.
But, yes, I'm still your loyal friend.
I always have been, and always will be.
I... I tried to free you, and I did.
I sent the witch Shiori here
to free you, and she did.
But I didn't know she was friends with Kiara,
and would summon her here if threatened.
I thought she would come alone.
This was not supposed to happen.
It was not my intention.
You sent... a witch to free me?
Why would you send one
who binds my kind for power?
Of all those in the world... a witch?
Why not send one of my
most beloved followers?
Only they are said to be able to free me.
Explain yourself!
What's going on?
I'm... I'm sorry.
I have a lot to explain,
but we don't have time now. We need to go. Now!
Death is coming for you.
What?
Please...
Come with me.
I know a way in which we can hide from Death.
But we have to leave now, before it's too late.
I'm not going anywhere with you until you
explain to me what is going on.
Now!
Why would you send a witch to free me, IRyS?
Because... I had no choice!
You had no choice? You could have
sent one of my followers instead!
You don't have any more followers!
They're all dead!
They all died... long ago.
What?
No... That... That can't be.
Has it been that long?
It's been over a thousand years
since you've been locked away.
And your followers... they're all gone now.
It's been many long years since your name
was whispered in these lands.
You mean... they... no longer... love me?
I... I'm sorry.
I tried to free you as fast as I could. I really did.
But it took a long time to work out how to free you,
and there was so much going on.
And the Gods weren't about to look kindly on
any trying to undo their work, either.
I'm sorry. I don't have time to explain everything right now.
I understand.
But, IRyS...
Tell me...
...do you still love me?
What?
Yes, of course!
Then why do you lie to me?
I... I'm not lying, Nerissa!
Enough!
You, of all people, should understand...
...that a witch wouldn't be able to resist the power in my book and attempt to bind me.
And you can hardly expect me to believe...
...that you, one of both planes, didn't know of a witch's connection to such a famed warrior.
This wasn't an attempt to free me.
This... this was an attempt to kill me!
To be free of me, to do what the gods couldn't! Get back!
Nerissa, that's not true!
You don't understand!
Please give me some time to explain, but... but not here.
Death is coming for you! We have to go!
I'm not going anywhere with you!
Nerissa!
Surely by now, Kiara's soul has arrived before Death.
And when Death finds out that you are free again...
...we don't have much time! We have to go! Now!
Please, Nerissa!
No... I don't believe you.
You've broken my spirit.
To learn that my followers no longer love me was one thing...
...but to discover that my closest and most loyal friend has betrayed me...
...tried to kill me...
...and no longer loves me too...
If you no longer wish to give me your love...
...then I will take it!
遠ざかりはじめた
You began to drift away,
その背中はもう振り返らない
and that back of yours will never look back.
長い夜が明けても
Even after the long night breaks,
過ちと罪は今もずっと消えずに
my mistakes and sins still remain forever.
落ちる夕日 闇が忍び寄り
The setting sun sinks, and darkness creeps in,
黒く染まってゆく純粋
staining my pure heart in black.
想うほどに どうして傷で試した？
The more I cared, why did I test you with pain?
欲しかったのは唯一つ その笑顔なのに
When all I ever wanted was your smile.
何度間違い続けた日々を
Unraveling those days of endless mistakes
解いて結び直すように
as if trying to tie them back together,
迷っても会いに行くよ
I will go to see you, even if I lose my way.
悲しい涙は拭って
Wiping away those sad tears...
いつの間にか忘れていた
Searching for that gentle voice
その優しい声を探して
which I had forgotten before I knew it.
また手を取り合えたなら
If we can hold hands once more,
君ともう一度約束を交わそう
let's make a promise together again.
途切れそうな可能性
This faint possibility, on the verge of fading,
見失わないように追いかけて
I'll chase after it so I won't lose sight of it.
手に入れたものなら
If it's something I've obtained,
理想とは違う どこか欠けた愛情
it's different from my ideal—an affection chipped somewhere.
怒り 嘆き 歪めたまま
Unleashing anger and grief
ぶつけ合う 逆さまの言葉
at each other, in twisted, reversed words.
想うほどに どうして許せなかった？
The more I cared, why couldn't I forgive you?
守りたかった笑顔を 気付けば壊して
Realizing I had broken the smile I wanted to protect.
たとえすれ違い離れてても
Even if we pass by and drift apart,
君を信じられたなら
if I could only believe in you,
また会える日が来るから
the day we meet again will surely come.
二人 懐かしい顔で
Both of us with nostalgic faces...
何気なく過ごしていた
Recalling those moments
あの時を思い返すなら
we spent together so casually.
ありのまま通じ合えた
We understood each other just as we were,
まるで運命かのように
as if it were truly destiny.
失くしたものかも
Even if it's something lost,
戻らないことわかっていても
and I know it will never return,
願いをかけること止められはしない いつか
I can't stop making a wish that someday...
どれほど大切な人だったのか
Just how precious you were to me,
胸が苦しむたびに知った
I realized every time my heart ached.
ともに過ごした日を
The days we spent together...
笑い合えた日々を
The days we laughed together,
何度も間違い続けた日々を
The days we kept making mistakes,
ほどいて結びなおすように
Let's untie and tie them back together again,
迷っても会いにいくよ
Even if I get lost, I will go to see you,
哀しい涙は拭って
Wiping away those sad tears.
いつのまにか連れていくんだ
Before we knew it, it's taking us away,
その優しい声を探して
Searching for that gentle voice.
また手を取り合えたなら
If we could hold hands again,
君ともう一度約束を交わそう
I'd make a promise with you once more.
Kiara... dead?
Never thought I'd see the day.
But tell me, what laid you low?
I must know, as there are few that could bring this about,
and even fewer who would give you reason to voyage on through my blackened halls and not return to the world of the living as a hatchling.
Must be urgent, whatever it is.
Forgive me, but I felt this was something you needed to hear urgently.
I was slain by one with whom you are quite familiar.
A tyrant of darkness, one out to bring all the world under her domain...
...to worship her for all eternity.
It can't be.
I'm afraid the Demon of Sound has been freed from the void again and is in the world once more.
Her long confinement has ended, and she is the same as she has ever been:
quick to anger, blinded by her lust for adoration.
And this time, I was the second victim of her lust for love and blood.
You... murdered by that love-obsessed demon?
Yes.
And her first victim was a good friend of mine, too.
Forgive me, Lord Death, but this injustice cannot stand!
Unfortunately, her power is already beyond my ability to stop.
Please, you must do something to stop that demon...
...that monster! She will surely only take more lives...
...and plunge the world into further chaos.
Come on, quick! Ascend to the world of the living with your great scythe in hand...
...and reap the life of the Demon of Sound before she can claim another victim!
Avenge my life and the life of my friend. I beg you.
That demon cannot be left to ravage the world once more.
I warned the other gods before, but here we are.
It is time I take this into my own hands and do what I should have done long ago.
Your demonic side was always to be the death of you, IRyS.
Don't you dare speak her name.
Silence!
Your bloodlust and desire for adoration has clouded your judgment...
...to the point where you can't even tell friend from foe anymore.
You're the one who brought bloody doom upon your own beloved friend...
...and yourself.
Your fear of losing your hold over things brings about the very result you so fear.
How dare you!
Continue on with your excuses, blame who you will for your own misdoing if you wish.
In the end, you have only yourself to blame for the situation you find yourself in.
A lust for love so strong, that those you love turn away.
A desire for power so overwhelming...
...those you have power over, turn on you.
An anger so deep, that you destroy all who might have helped save you.
Your fate has been sealed by your own hand.
And now, I am now here to deliver it to you.
Why do you get to decide who lives or dies?
You, who sits alone in your own realm...
...Empress of all, both life and death at your fingertips?
What could you possibly know
about the desire for the love and adoration of others?
You, who already has everything.
You, and all the gods, all full of yourselves...
and so ready to look down upon those of us who fight for more.
Mouths full of twisted tongues...
Their hearts rot with jealousy.
They're jealous...
of me!
Spiteful... that I was loved more!
Again, you cannot see past your own desires.
The gods took pity on you and your kind.
When I created you, the first demon,
the gods felt it unjust and dangerous for such a being to exist...
for the sole purpose of watching over the surface in my stead.
To be mindless... soulless.
So,
they gave the demon a psyche, and plucked it from my deepest and blackest halls,
freeing it to roam amongst the two worlds whenever it pleased.
I warned them that the demonic nature was too strong and dangerous to give such desires,
and far too dangerous for such a being to exist alongside the mortals.
But...
the others persisted, and now...
here we are.
My unheeded warnings leading us back to where it all started.
You almost plunged the world into chaos due to your unbridled lust for adoration.
Time and time again, you gave in to your nature.
Banishing you to the Void was supposed to be a chance for you to reflect on your past,
but it has only proven that you are truly...
unfit for this world.
アイアイエチュ　ナナナナナですの
I-I-H-U, n-n-n-n-no is the answer
君がいなけりゃあたしは無い無い
Without you, I am nothing, nothing
はいはいそうですねその通りです
Yes, yes, that's right, exactly
喉を過ぎればそれは真実
Once it passes your throat, it becomes the truth
アイアイエチュ　ナナナナナですの
I-I-H-U, n-n-n-n-no is the answer
君は軽薄　くたびれだらけ
You are frivolous, full of fatigue
あたし一じゃいられない
I can't just be alone
それは常にひしひし
I constantly feel it deep down
あなたはわいわい　どうにでもなってな保存
You're making a racket, let it all go to ruin
だめですの
That's a no-no
意味があるなら言葉にせずに
If there is meaning, don't put it in words
愉しい態度で示してくれ
Show me with an enjoyable attitude
全てが伝わらないままでいい
It's fine if everything remains uncommunicated
トップシークレット
Top secret
明かさないように
Try not to reveal it
あたしがいない無い
I am nothing, nothing
はいはいそうですねその通りです
Yes, yes, that's right, exactly
喉を過ぎればそれは真実
Once it passes your throat, it becomes the truth
あるべき場所へ
To where it belongs
あたし導く
Lead me
奈落の底で
To the bottom of the abyss
アイアイエチュなんですの
I-I-H-U, that's what it is
アイアイエチュ　ナナナナナですの
I-I-H-U, n-n-n-n-no is the answer
やはり軽薄　お気の毒あたし
Just as frivolous, poor me
可愛いと不健康を引き摺るの
Dragging cute and unhealthy along
君が今更会いたいのだな
Wanting to see you now of all times, huh?
トップシークレット
Top secret
喉を焼け焦がす
Scorch my throat
秘密にまにあう
Make it in time for the secret
来ないで
Don't come
アイアイエチュ　ナナナナナですの
I-I-H-U, n-n-n-n-no is the answer
君がいるからあたしが痛い痛い
Because you are here, I am hurting, hurting
はいはいそうですねその通りです
Yes, yes, that's right, exactly
よくおできだね
You did a fine job
アイアイエチュ　ナナナナナですの
I-I-H-U, n-n-n-n-no is the answer
あたし痛い痛い痛いエチュですの
I'm hurting, hurting, hurting, I-H-U
どうにもならぬ
Can't do anything about it
アイアイエチュ　ナナナナナですの
I-I-H-U, n-n-n-n-no is the answer
君がいなけりゃあたしは無い無い
Without you, I am nothing, nothing
はいはいそうですねその通りです
Yes, yes, that's right, exactly
喉を過ぎればそれは真実
Once it passes your throat, it becomes the truth
あるべき場所へ
To where it belongs
あたし導く
Lead me
アイアイエチュ
I-I-H-U
あ、あ、あ、あ
Ah, ah, ah, ah
奈落の底まで
To the bottom of hell
あ、あ、あ、あ、あ、あ
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Oh, such a misguided fool.
Your reckless ways have brought black doom upon yourself and those most beloved around you.
Blaming your misery on others when your demise was, in fact, forged by your own hands.
While you have earned your death in full...
...it is with pity, not anger...
...that this blade falls upon you.
街明かり華やか エーテル麻酔の冷たさ
The bustling city and its neon lights, a touch of ether that's cold as ice
眠れない午前二時 全てが急速に変わる
It's 2 AM and I can hardly sleep cause everything keeps changing rapidly
オイル切れのライター
I'm like a lighter that's all out of gas
焼けつくような胃の中
My insides are on fire
全てがそう嘘なら
If only everything was a lie
本当によかったのにね
Things would be so much better
君の首を絞める夢を見た
I had a dream where these hands of mine were strangling your neck
光の溢れる昼下がり
On a bright, sunny afternoon
君の細い喉が跳ねるのを
I watched your slender throat twitch
泣き出しそうな眼で見ていた
As my eyes welled up with tears
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたいと思う
I want to throw myself into a nuclear reactor
真っ青な光包まれて綺麗
And its pale blue light would envelop me so beautifully
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら そしたら
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor
すべてが許されるような気がして
Then everything might be okay, I might be forgiven
ベランダの向こう側 階段を昇ってゆく音
On the other side of the veranda, I hear footsteps ascending the stairs
陰りだした空が 窓ガラスに部屋に落ちる
As the clouds creep over the sunlight, it drips through my window and into my room
拡散する夕暮れ 泣き腫らしたような陽の赤
Twilight scatters across the horizon, red like eyes swollen by tears
融けるように少しずつ
Slowly but surely, it's melting away
少しずつ死んでゆく世界
Slowly but steadily, the world is dying
君の首を絞める夢を見た
I had a dream where these hands of mine were strangling your neck
春風に揺れるカーテン
My curtains were swaying gently in the spring breeze
乾いて切れた唇から
Your dry, parched lips mustered up
零れる言葉は泡のよう
Words that would vanish like foam on the waves
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたいと思う
I want to throw myself into a nuclear reactor
真っ白に記憶 融かされて消える
Into the shining, white light my memories will fade and disappear
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor
また昔みたいに 眠れるような そんな気がして
I might be able to sleep like I used to and everything might be okay
時計の秒針や テレビの司会者や
The second hand on the clock, and the host on the television
そこにいるけど
There's someone there
見えない誰かの
But I just can't see them
笑い声 飽和して反響する
Their laughter swells and grows into an endless echo
アレグロ・アジテート
Allegro agitate
耳鳴りが消えない 止まらない
The ringing in my ears won't stop, it won't go away
アレグロ・アジテート
Allegro agitate
耳鳴りが消えない 止まらない
The ringing in my ears won't stop, it won't go away
誰もみんな消えてく夢を見た
I had a dream where the whole entire world disappeared
真夜中の部屋の広さと静寂が
Tonight, I'm swallowed by the vastness of my dark room
胸につっかえて
Yet, silence closes in and suffocates me
上手く息ができなくなる
My lungs can't find the air I need to breathe
核融合炉にさ
If I could throw myself...
飛び込んでみたら そしたら
...into a nuclear reactor.
きっと眠るように消えていけるんだ
Then I could finally fade away, as easily as closing my eyes to sleep.
僕のいない朝は 今よりずっと素晴らしくて
A new dawn without me would surely be a dazzling new day.
全ての歯車が噛み合った
All of the gears would be turning together in harmony.
きっとそんな世界だ
Surely, that's how the world would be.
Hi darlings, and welcome to my 3D concert!
My first technically solo one! Uh, as you can see up here...
...is the hashtag for today, which is #RequiemforLove3D!
I-I'm watching the chat. Did you guys enjoy it?
Did you like it? Did you have fun? I sure hope so!
Well, um, obviously, a lot just happened.
But I must let you all know, this was all a musical.
So none of it was real.
I didn't... no one is... no one is hurt.
There were no Hololive girls hurt...
...in the making of this musical.
So please don't worry!
Um, this stage is awesome! So I want to give it up to...
...the team over at, uh, Hololive Productions,
...who put this all together.
Can we just take a look, take a moment
...to admire this beautiful stage before us?
Uh, some of the more lesser-shown details,
...I kind of wanted to, to highlight a little bit.
So, um, let's go ahead and take a look at, uh, mayhaps the moon, maybe?
Look at that big thing in the background.
It was also dark red at one point, but...
...currently it is, as it probably should be,
...uh, normal, beautiful, because I was cured. So...
We also have the giant castle in the background...
...which is, oh my gosh, I was so excited for this.
I was like, "Oh, I want something that's really kind of like..."
...cathedral-esque and, and dark and gothic."
And they fully delivered! I'm so, so pleased...
...with how it ended up looking in the final. So...
So happy! Uh, we also have the beautiful stained glass.
If you take a look, it's, uh, back there.
These ones were actually screens, but we also have the ones on the side...
...that were, uh, a little bit broken,
...but could also change as well, so...
Very, very fun! It was kind of something that I was like,
"Oh, I wonder how it's gonna go." But I think it ended up looking really cool, right?
...lastly, we have all of these lovely flowers out in front.
Um, lastly, we have all of these lovely flowers out in front.
Uh, I just thought they came out so pretty,
...and I like how they kind of change throughout, so...
It just kind of looked like nothingness, like a little void of like dead plants,
...but then at the end they all bloomed, and it was so beautiful, and, oh my gosh...
I'm so nervous!
Uh, you might have noticed also, something's a little different about me today.
Do you see anything... different?
My wings are out!
I-I decided, since we've known each other
...for kind of a long time now, that maybe it was finally time to...
...uh, stop pretending they're a coat and actually show you what they were.
But I did decide to take off my arm... armors a little bit, just cuz...
...you know, I was feeling a little warm after all of that movement, so...
...I'd love to show you the wings!
So I'm going to open them up for you,
...and to try flying for a little bit, so...
Yeah, there we go!
What do you think? I am capable...
...of flight.
Obviously, it's a little...
It's a little slow...
...but I'm working on it. I'm working on my muscles. So...
We'll... I'll figure it out eventually. It's been a while. I was locked up for like...
...9,000 years. Cut me some slack!
Well, this is all very exciting, so again, I'm so happy to have you here.
I wanted to talk a little bit about... I have an announcement after this, but before that...
...I wanted to talk a little bit about... just the making of this.
Whoa! We had so many lovely guests, first and foremost.
First, we started off with Shiori Novella, who was our beautiful, cute witch...
...who came here maybe not knowing what she was getting into.
Then, we had Takanashi Kiara, the brave, amazing Phoenix...
...came in trying to avenge her friend...
...but ended up getting bested by the best.
Then we had IRyS, my Nephilim friend.
Friends as we are both demons, kind of.
And then, last but not least, of course, we had...
...Mori Calliope come in and... take my life, as she should have...
...because wow, I was kind of... I was kind of mean in that musical, don't you think?
Not... not exactly the way that I usually am, so kind, but...
Regardless, it was really fun.
I came up with the idea for the story, and I wanted something that was like...
...a little more exciting, a little more chunibyo.
Because deep down, I am cringe, but I am free, so...
I hope you enjoyed the concept. We had amazing scriptwriters...
...and just the whole team working on all of this was so amazing.
So thank you for everyone who put in their efforts into this. It seriously means so much to me.
And... audience, Jailbirds, thank you so much for watching. I hope you had a wonderful time.
And now, it is time for an important announcement!
This is my celebration merch...
...Nerissa Ravencroft 850,000 Subscribers Celebration!
So, let's go ahead and take a look at the details. Next up...
...or first up, I suppose.
"Your assignment has arrived."
This is a plush blanket featuring an illustration by...
...basically my second mama, Yomosaka at this point...
...who also did the promotional art, or the... the like main cover art for this musical today.
Um, so it's very lovely.
All of the merch today is going to be themed off of the DEO outfit.
Again, so beautiful, so gorgeous. You can cuddle up with it at night...
...if you're feeling lonesome, so highly recommend grabbing it.
Next up!
We have the DEO Nerissa voice keychain.
This illustration is by noka.
This is a cute keychain, of course, you can carry it around with you everywhere.
And, in case you miss the sound of my voice...
...it has my voice in it.
About six different voice samples, so you can click click click click click...
...and hear me say different, varying, funny little things, so do consider it.
Next up is...
...the Nerissa Ravencroft hand puppet.
Um, I really wanted one, and I thought you guys would too.
And especially with this sexy DEO outfit, I just thought it made sense, so...
Do think about the puppet shows that you could put on with me as your starring puppet.
Think about it, consider the possibilities.
So, that is the first one... first one? That is one of the last ones, but next up...
...is the last item, which is the "Match with Me" necklace.
This features the necklace from my DEO outfit.
It is silver and it has a tiny amethyst-colored gem, because...
...it's kind of hard to tell, but the gem on my actual necklace is not red...
...it is actually kind of purple-y, so please look forward to it.
Next up...
...is the Complete Set Purchase Bonus.
Um, limited edition version. It's going to come with a postcard...
...with a handwritten autograph by yours truly.
And of course, the art is going to be the same one that's featured in the plush blanket...
...the art by Yomosaka-san.
So, please do consider getting it, if you want the whole set, if you want the limited set.
Um, next up is the regular complete set.
This is going to come with a postcard with a duplicated foil-stamped autograph by me...
...in the case that you miss out on the limited.
But you'll still get my signature either way, so don't worry too much.
And both the limited and complete set...
...are going to be coming with a bonus voice pack...
...called "A Late Night at the Office"...
...featuring me, of course, and you, who works in my office, Jailbird, so...
That is all of my merchandise! Please please buy it. I hope you like it.
Again, this is a celebration for 850,000K.
And I would be remiss to not say that this is all thanks to you guys and your support.
So thank you so so much for supporting me, for...
...following me, for...
watching my covers, for watching this today,
watching my streams, commenting...
everything you guys do, I am so grateful.
So, thank you so much! So,
that's the... the final full set.
And... and yeah!
It's... it's all good, so...
please buy it.
I hope you guys like it. I hope you're
looking forward to receiving the items,
if you're buying it. They will go live
right after this, I believe, so
go ahead and check the description.
It should have all the information right below.
So, thank you all so much! And that's that.
So, I guess I should say goodbye.
So...
I don't want to, though. I'm having so much fun
today dancing with everyone
and singing for you guys, and...
But I'm so grateful I could spend time with you
and share this special moment with you.
I hope you guys all had a lot of fun,
and I look forward to seeing you all
in my next stream.
So, for now, bye, darlings!
REQUIEM for LOVE